// (function() {
// var questions = [{

// question: "What year did Belize gain Independence?",
// answers: ["1981", "1961", "1931"],
// correctAnswer: 0

// }, {

// question: "Where is Belize located?",
// answers: ["South America", "Central America", "North America"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// }, {

// question: "What civilization occupied Belize prior to the 15th century?",
// answers: ["Olmec", "Aztec", "Maya"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "What animal was discovered in Belize in the 1920s?",
// answers: ["Jaguar", "Tapir", "Iguana"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "Where was the Mitchell-Hedges crystal Skull discovered?",
// answers: ["Lamanai", "Lubaantun", "Cahal Pech"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "Where was the jade head discovered in Belize?",
// answers: ["Xunantunich", "Caracol", "Altun Ha"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "What Mayan city was inhabited for more than two thousand years?",
// answers: ["Lubaantun", "Lamanai", "Altun Ha"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{  


// question: "What is the highest honour awarded by the government of Belize?",
// answers: ["Order of the National Hero", "Order of Belize", "Order of Distinction"],
// correctAnswer: 0

// },{

// question: "What was the name of Belize before it was changed in 1973?",
// answers: ["Saint George", "British Honduras", "New Britain"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "What tree appears on the Belize flag?",
// answers: ["Mangrove", "Mahagony", "Ziricote"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "Belize shares a land border with which country?",
// answers: ["Honduras", "Mexico", "Nicaragua"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "What is the name of the largest sinkhole in the world?",
// answers: ["The blue Hole ", "The Big Hole", "The Crater"],
// correctAnswer: 0

// },{

// question: "Which is the capital of Belize?",
// answers: ["Belize City", "Belmopan", "Belama"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: " When is Independence Day in Belize??",
// answers: ["10 September", "21 September", "15 September"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "What date is Baron Bliss Day in Belize?",
// answers: ["	9 March", "1 April", "10 September"],
// correctAnswer: 0

// },{

// question: "Who was the first Governor General of independent Belize??",
// answers: ["Colville Young", "George Price", "Minita Gordon"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "What is the official language of Belize",
// answers: ["Spanish", "French", "English"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "What year was the crystal skull discovered?",
// answers: ["1946", "1924", "1865"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "What year was the Jade Head discovered?",
// answers: ["1868", "1928", "1968"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "Who were the Europeans that successfully settled Belize?",
// answers: ["Spanish", "French", "British"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "In the early 1700s, what made Belize the wealthiest British settlement in the Caribbean?",
// answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "After logwood declined,  the settlers in Belize started to harvested what other product?",
// answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

// question: "When did the Spanish last attack the  British settlers in Belize?",
// answers: ["21 September 1925", "10 September 1961", "10 September 1798"],
// correctAnswer: 2

// },{

// question: "What does the name “Belize” mean?",
// answers: ["Muddy water", "Blue water", "Green River"],
// correctAnswer: 0

// },{

// question: "What is the highest elevation in the Cockscomb Range at 3,681 feet or 1,122 m high?",
// answers: ["The Falls", "Victoria Peak", "Mountain Pine Ridge"],
// correctAnswer: 1

// },{

//     question: "In the early 1700s, what made Belize the wealthiest British settlement in the Caribbean?",
//     answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
//     correctAnswer: 2

// },{

//     question: "In the early 1700s, what made Belize the wealthiest British settlement in the Caribbean?",
//     answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
//     correctAnswer: 2

// },{

//     question: "In the early 1700s, what made Belize the wealthiest British settlement in the Caribbean?",
//     answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
//     correctAnswer: 2

// },{

//     question: "In the early 1700s, what made Belize the wealthiest British settlement in the Caribbean?",
//     answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
//     correctAnswer: 2

// },{

//     question: "In the early 1700s, what made Belize the wealthiest British settlement in the Caribbean?",
//     answers: ["Sugarcane", "Mahogany", "Logwood"],
//     correctAnswer: 2

// }];